Hello everyone and welcome back to my channel, so
friends,
you will have to pay for the percentage of tyre that you mean is worn out or worn out, so
I said sir, this was
not discussed earlier, I had told him earlier also,
sir, you people are adding it in this,
maybe that cover was more than 4-5000, so at
that time I said sir, do not add mine
because I will have to pay for it, then at that
time they said no sir,
we will change it for you free of cost, so there were
these hidden charges in it, so
my tyre was worn out for around 50 percent, so
I had to pay a cost of around 8000
and had to pay 000 file charges,
after that what is the name, I got a
new tyre, like this is a little
worn out tyre and this was a new tyre, the one on the
back was torn, they
gave me a brand new tyre and it is of the same company, there is
absolutely no problem in it, but the
charges are around 00, I had to pay a
new one for 14000 in the market  I would have got the tyre
and my no claim bonus would have also gone along with
this I had to face the same problem,
this tyre costed me around 15000, I had to pay 15-16000,
if I had bought it otherwise it would have cost the same
but I was not aware of it at that time so
I took
this tyre in claim, so beware of this scam, this
claim of tyre protection,
friends, you will often find it to be a waste,
I did
not find it that much beneficial because you have to pay for the amount of wear out, as much as
your tyre gets worn out
and if you buy tyres of any good company like
Joma, after market
or B stone, then you
get the same warranty of 1 year, so in that also
you have to pay for the worn out part of the tyre and they do not give you the rest, no matter how it is torn, how it is cut, there is a
complete guarantee of tearing in it,
so I would
say that you should opt out of this option from
your policy because it is very
heavy for me  At that time
I had given Rs 10000 extra than the premium, so
this was a video from my side for you people
so that you people remain alert and stay away from such scams,
so this was all in the video, I hope
you liked the video, if you liked the video then
like the video, share it and
subscribe to the channel, if you have any question then do
ask in the comments, thank you so much.